const level8Questions = [
  {
        question: "Quýt",
        answers: ["橘子 (júzi)", "怎么 (zěnme)"],
        correct: "橘子 (júzi)",
    },
    {
        question: "Tổng cộng",
        answers: ["一共 (yígòng)", "两 (liǎng)"],
        correct: "一共 (yígòng)",
    },
    {
        question: "Đưa, cho",
        answers: ["给 (gěi)", "找 (zhǎo)"],
        correct: "给 (gěi)",
    },
    {
        question: "Buổi chiều",
        answers: ["下午 (xiàwǔ)", "上午 (shàngwǔ)"],
        correct: "下午 (xiàwǔ)",
    },
    {
        question: "Thư viện",
        answers: ["图书馆 (túshūguǎn)", "营业员 (yíngyèyuán)"],
        correct: "图书馆 (túshūguǎn)",
    },
    {
        question: "Đổi, trao đổi",
        answers: ["换 (huàn)", "小姐 (xiǎojiě)"],
        correct: "换 (huàn)",
    },
    {
        question: "Nhân dân tệ",
        answers: ["人民币 (Rénmínbì)", "人民 (rénmín)"],
        correct: "人民币 (Rénmínbì)",
    },
    {
        question: "Nghìn",
        answers: ["百 (bǎi)", "千 (qiān)"],
        correct: "千 (qiān)",
    },
    {
        question: "Vạn",
        answers: ["万 (wàn)", "百 (bǎi)"],
        correct: "万 (wàn)",
    },
    {
        question: "Đô la mỹ, USD",
        answers: ["美元 (Měiyuán)", "港币 (Gǎngbì)"],
        correct: "美元 (Měiyuán)",
    },
    {
        question: "EURO",
        answers: ["日元 (Rìyuán)", "欧元 (Ōuyuán)"],
        correct: "欧元 (Ōuyuán)",
    },
    {
        question: "Chờ, đợi/ vv...",
        answers: ["等 (děng)", "一会儿 (yíhuìr)"],
        correct: "等 (děng)",
    },
    {
        question: "Tiên shinh",
        answers: ["先生 (xiānsheng)", "数 (shù / shǔ)"],
        correct: "先生 (xiānsheng)",
    },
    {
        question: "Làm việc văn phòng",
        answers: ["办公室 (bàngōngshì)", "办公 (bàngōng)"],
        correct: "办公 (bàngōng)",
    },
    {
        question: "Nhân viên",
        answers: ["职员 (zhíyuán)", "找 (zhǎo)"],
        correct: "职员 (zhíyuán)",
    },
    {
        question: "Tìm, trả lại tiền thừa",
        answers: ["找 (zhǎo)", "在 (zài)"],
        correct: "找 (zhǎo)",
    },
];

export default level8Questions;
